Guide to the Everett Education Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- United Teachers of Everett records, 1986-1990; 3849-004; 1.61 cubic feet
  - Comments of Rossman's "As I See It", Undated (Box-folder 2/70)
  - Comments on Mike Sell's Visits to Schools and February 13th Walkout, 1989 (Box-folder 2/71)
  - February 13th Walkout Information, 1990 (Box-folder 2/72)
  - Walkout Assessments, 1990 (Box-folder 2/73)
  - Walkout Building Leaders, 1990 (Box-folder 2/74)
  - Walkout Committee-Names of Helpers in other Districts, Undated (Box-folder 2/75)
  - Volunteers for February 13th Walkout, 1989 (Box-folder 2/76)
  - February 13th Walkout Information Part 1 of 3, 1990 (Box-folder 3/1)
  - February 13th Walkout Information Part 2 of 3, 1990 (Box-folder 3/2)
  - February 13th Walkout Information Part 3 of 3, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 3/3)
  - February 13th Walkout T-Shirt Ideas, 1990 (Box-folder 3/4)
  - Teacher Aid Information, 1983 (Box-folder 3/5)
  - Principal Responses to Elementary Staff Time, 1989 (Box-folder 3/6)
  - Response to Hearing Impaired Service Complaint, 1985 (Box-folder 3/7)
  - Comments on Change to WAC 315, 1989 (Box-folder 3/8)
  - Barrier Resolution Committee Members Report, 1989 (Box-folder 3/9)
  - Building Organization Checklist, Undated (Box-folder 3/10)
  - Comments on Action Alert Volume 89-90 Number 2, 1989 (Box-folder 3/11)
  - Insurance Committee, 1984 (Box-folder 3/12)
  - Letters to the Editor and Legislators, Funding Concerns, 1989 (Box-folder 3/13)
  - 1989-90 Calendar Survey (Box-folder 3/14)
  - 1989-90 Budget Survey (Box-folder 3/15)
  - Candidate Statements and Nominations, 1989 (Box-folder 3/16)
  - Officer and Delegate Nominations, 1989 (Box-folder 3/17)
  - Task Force on More Effective Schools Program, 1987 (Box-folder 3/18)
  - Effective Schools Evaluation, 1988 (Box-folder 3/19)
  - Elementary Conference Survey Results, 1988 (Box-folder 3/20)
  - Eisenhower Middle School Request for Insurance Change, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 3/21)
  - Follow-Up Survey on Kindergarten Conferences, 1987 (Box-folder 3/22)
  - Compilation of Late Start Day Survey, 1987 (Box-folder 3/23)
- Everett Education Association. United Teachers of Everett records, 1978-1992; 3849-005; 6.00 cubic feet
  Correspondence, minutes, agenda, dues files, reports, newsletters, surveys, subject series.
  Donated by the Association, 9/23/1992.
  - CORRESPONDENCE, 1985-1990; SERIES I (Box-folder 1/1-3/28)
    - Correspondence, Incoming - President Mike Sells, 1986-1987; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/1-1/4)
      - Mike Sells Incoming Correspondence, Part 1 of 3, 1986 (Box-folder 1/1)
      - Mike Sells Incoming Correspondence, Part 2 of 3, 1986 (Box-folder 1/2)
      - Mike Sells Incoming Correspondence, Part 3 of 3, 1986 (Box-folder 1/3)
      - "PILCHUCK" Uniserv Council and Legislation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Correspondence, Outgoing - President Mike Sells, 1986-1987; Subseries B (Box-folder 1/5-1/6)
      - Mike Sells Outgoing Correspondence, Part 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Mike Sells Outgoing Correspondence, Part 2 of 2, 1986 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Correspondence - Everett Education Association (Includes various Operation PILCHUCK Materials), 1985-1990; Subseries C (Box-folder 1/7-3/28)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence from United Teachers of Everett, 1987 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, Part 1 of 3, 1987 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, Part 2 of 3, 1987 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, Part 3 of 3, 1987 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - "PILCHUCK": Dues, Meetings, and Negotiations, 1987 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - "PILCHUCK": Initiatives and Legislation, 1987 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence, Part 1 of 2, 1987 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence, Part 2 of 2, 1987 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 1/15)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 1/16)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 1/17)
      - "PILCHUCK": Reports, Meetings, Surveys, and Miscellaneous Valuable Information, 1987 (Box-folder 1/18)
      - "PILCHUCK": Budget, Meetings, and Bargaining, 1987 (Box-folder 1/19)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence to United Teachers of Everett 1987-1988, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 1/20)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence to United Teachers of Everett 1987-1988, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence to United Teachers of Everett 1987-1988, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 1/22)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Everett Education Association Incoming Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - "PILCHUCK" Meetings and Agendas, 1988 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - Everett Education Association Outgoing Correspondence, 1987-1988, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Correspondence - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett, 1985-1990; Subseries D (Box-folder 2/1-3/28)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/1)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/2)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/3)
      - "PILCHUCK": Goals, Budget, and Agenda, 1988 (Box-folder 2/4)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/6)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 1, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/7)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/8)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/9)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/10)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings and Agendas, 1989 (Box-folder 2/11)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/12)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/13)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 2 of 2, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings, Leases, and Agendas, 1988 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 1 of 3: Thank you letters and Insurance Info (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 2, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 3, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 3, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - "PILCHUCK": Bargaining Goals, Meetings, Timelines, and Recommendations, 1989 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 3, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 3, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 3, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 4, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 2/27)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 4, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 4, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 2/29)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings, Programs, Budget Reports, and Salary Issues, 1989 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 4, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1988-1989 Book 4, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990, Part 1 of 3 (Box-folder 3/1)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990, Part 2 of 3 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990, Part 3 of 3 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Everett Education Association/United teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 3/5)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings, Political Action Committee, and Procedures, 1989 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 1 of 4 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 2 of 4 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 3 of 4 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 4 of 4 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 2, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 2, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 3/12)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings, Contracts, Agenda, and Proposals, 1989 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 3, Part 1 of 2 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 3, Part 2 of 2 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Everett Education Association/United teachers of Everett Incoming Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 4 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - "PILCHUCK": Meetings, Goals, Action 1991, and Budget, 1990 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 4, Part 1 of 4 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 4, Part 2 of 4 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 4, Part 3 of 4 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Outgoing Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 4, Part 4 of 4 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 1 of 5: Memos, Reports, and Bulletins (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 2 of 5: Recommendations, Agendas, and Reports (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 3 of 5: AIDS Prevention Curriculum, Recommendations, and Budget Summary (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 4 of 5: Planning, Enrollment, and Agendas (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 1, Part 5 of 5: Requests, Resolutions, and Recommendations (Box-folder 3/26)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 2, Part 1 of 2: Pamphlets, Agendas, Recommendations, and Rental Rates (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Everett School District #2 Correspondence, 1989-1990 Book 2, Part 2 of 2: Resolutions, Recommendations, Budget Proposal, and Voucher Register (Box-folder 3/28)
  - MEETING AGENDAS AND MINUTES, 1986-1991; SERIES II (Box-folder 4/1-4/11)
    - Executive Board Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Representative Council Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Executive Board Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Representative Council Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Executive Board Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Representative Council Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1988-1089 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Executive Board Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Representative Council Meeting Agenda and Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Building Leaders Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 1990 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Washington Education Association Agenda and Funding Information, 1991 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Membership Meeting, Personnel, and School Lists, 1991 (Box-folder 4/11)
  - PUBLICATIONS, NEWSLETTERS, AND FLYERS, 1986-1990; SERIES III (Box-folder 4/12-4/28)
    - Publications and Flyers, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - Outside Publications, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - Everett Education Association Publications- Originals Part 1 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Everett Education Association Publications- Originals Part 2 of 2, 1986 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Political Action and Legislation, 1987 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Publications and Flyers, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Political Action and Information, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Publications and Flyers- Originals and Copies Part 1 of 2, 1988 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Publications and Flyers- Originals and Copies Part 2 of 2, 1987 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - Outside Publications, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Publications and Flyers, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Outside Publications, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Publications and Flyers- Masters Part 1 of 2, 1989 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - Publications and Flyers- Masters Part 2 of 2, 1988 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - Publications and Flyers, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Outside Publications, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Election Alert: Advisory Summary, 1992 (Box-folder 4/28)
  - SURVEYS, QUESTIONNAIRES, AND REPORTS ON SURVEYS, 1988-1991; SERIES IV (Box-folder 4/29-5/9)
    - Monroe Elementary Survey, 1988 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - 1988-1989 Salary Survey (Box-folder 4/30)
    - Action Alert: Extra Hours Survey Part 1 of 2, 1989 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - Action Alert: Extra Hours Survey Part 2 of 2, 1989 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - Elementary Time Changes Survey, 1989 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Comments on School Surveys, 1990 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Elementary Building Rep. Survey, 1990 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Comments on 1990-1991 Washington Education Association Survey, undated (Box-folder 4/36)
    - Comments on Class Size, undated (Box-folder 4/37)
    - Bargaining Alert #2 Survey Part 1 of 2, 1990 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - Bargaining Alert #2 Survey Part 2 of 2, 1990 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Bargaining Alert Comments and Concerns, 1990 (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Elementary Planning Time Survey, 1991 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Petition to the Legislature and Governor, 1991 (Box-folder 4/42)
    - New Calendar Survey Part 1 of 4, undated (Box-folder 5/1)
    - New Calendar Survey Part 2 of 4, undated (Box-folder 5/2)
    - New Calendar Survey Part 3 of 4, undated (Box-folder 5/3)
    - New Calendar Survey Part 4 of 4, undated (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Survey Questions Part 1 of 5, undated (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Survey Questions Part 2 of 5, undated (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Survey Questions Part 3 of 5, undated (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Survey Questions Part 4 of 5, undated (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Survey Questions Part 5 of 5, undated (Box-folder 5/9)
  - DUES FILES (Includes Dues-Related Correspondence), 1985-1991; SERIES V (Box-folder 5/10-5/26)
    - 1986-1987 National Education Association/PAC Enrollment Form, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - 1986-1987 PULSE Opt-Outs (Box-folder 5/11)
    - 1986-1987 Cash Members (Box-folder 5/12)
    - 1986-1987 Membership Dues (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett 1986-1987 Agency Shop Fee Payers (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett 1987-1988 Cash Members (Box-folder 5/15)
    - 1987-1988 PULSE Opt-Outs (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Washington Education Association Dues Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Agency Shop Fee Payers, 1988 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - 1988-1989 Agency Shop Fees (Box-folder 5/19)
    - 1988-1989 Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Dues Information (Box-folder 5/20)
    - 1988-1989 Washington Education Association Dues (Box-folder 5/21)
    - 1988-1989 PULSE Opt-Outs (Box-folder 5/22)
    - PULSE Opt-Out Lists, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - 1989-1990 Washington Education Association Dues (Box-folder 5/24)
    - PULSE Opt-Out Forms sent to Washington Education Association/PULSE, 1990 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - PULSE Opt-Outs, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5/26)
  - REPORTS, 1986-1991; SERIES VI (Box-folder 5/27-5/39)
    - Indoor Air Quality of Schools, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - 1986-1987 Budget (Box-folder 5/28)
    - 1987-1988 Budget (Box-folder 5/29)
    - 1988-1989 Budget (Box-folder 5/30)
    - 1989-1990 Budget (Box-folder 5/31)
    - Washington Education Association Research Report 13 Certified Extra Duty Employees’ Schedules part 1 of 2, 1989 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Washington Education Association Research Report 13 Certified Extra Duty Employees’ Schedules part 2 of 2, 1989 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Washington Education Association Research Report 14 Classified Employees’ Wages for 1988-1989 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - TRI Settlement Updates and Washington Education Association's Allocation Model Packet, 1989 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Statewide Task Force Report: Addressing the Shortage of Physical and Occupational Therapists in the Schools of Washington, 1989 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Garfield Indoor Air Pollution Problem, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5/37)
    - Key Points from July 2nd Session, 1991 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Supplemental Budget Money Use, undated (Box-folder 5/39)
  - ASSOCIATION LEAVE DAYS, 1987-1989; SERIES VII (Box-folder 5/40-6/1)
    - Association Leave Days, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Association Leave Days, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 5/41)
    - Association Leave Days, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 5/42)
    - Association Leave Days, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 5/43)
    - Association Leave Days, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 5/44)
    - Association Leave Bill from Everett School District #2, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box-folder 5/45)
    - Snohomish County Metro Guide, 1991 (Box-folder 6/1)
  - RALLIES, STRIKES, AND POLITICAL ACTIONS, 1987-1992; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 6/2-6/13)
    - Political Action, 1988 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - July 13th Rally, 1990 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - Spring 1990 Negotiations (Box-folder 6/4)
    - Workers Memorial Day Official Certificate, 1990 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Collective Bargaining Between Everett Education Association and Everett School District- Draft, 1991 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - Strike Information Part 1 of 2, 1991 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - Strike Information Part 2 of 2, 1991 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - Action 1991 Logos (Box-folder 6/9)
    - P.M. Picketing, 1991 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - Informational Picketing of the 1990-1991 School Year (Box-folder 6/11)
    - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Election and Voting Information, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - Everett School District #2 Strategic Planning, 1990 (Box-folder 6/13)
  - SCHOOL STATISTICS AND INFORMATION, 1987-1990; SERIES IX (Box-folder 6/14-6/25)
    - Everett School District Staff Lists part 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - Everett School District Staff Lists part 2 of 2, 1987 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - Insurance Changes and Information, 1988 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - High School Band/Choral Stipend part 1 of 2, 1988 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - High School Band/Choral Stipend part 2 of 2, 1988 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - Building Lists, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - Schools for the 21st Century Project Abstracts, 1989 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - Silver Firs Elementary, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - Elementary Schedule, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - Silver Firs Elementary School, 1990 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - Jackson Elementary School, 1990 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - School Sign-In Sheets, undated (Box-folder 6/25)
  - COMMITTEES, CLUBS, ORGANIZATIONS, 1987-1992; SERIES X (Box-folder 6/27-6/38)
    - National Education Association/PAC Contributions, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - New Member Orientation Information, 1988 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - South Snohomish City Chamber Task Force, 1990 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Snohomish County Teacher Compensation Coalition, 1990 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - Comments to Lions Club, 1990 (Box-folder 6/30)
    - National Education Association Convention Nominations, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 6/31)
    - Washington Education Association/National Education Association Representative Nomination Forms, 1990 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Snohomish County Labor Council Services Committee, 1991 (Box-folder 6/33)
    - Washington Education Association Select Health Plans, 1991 (Box-folder 6/34)
    - Northwest Strategies-Ron Dotzauer, 1992 (Box-folder 6/35)
    - Washington Education Association Convention Delegates, 1992 (Box-folder 6/36)
    - Ed Deming Article, undated (Box-folder 6/37)
    - Everett Education Association/United Teachers of Everett Ballots and Voter Registration Sheets, undated (Box-folder 6/38)
  - LEGAL INFORMATION, 1978-1989; SERIES XI (Box-folder 6/39-6/41)
    - The Annotated Fiduciary: Materials on Fiduciary Responsibility and Prohibited Transactions Under ERISA, 1978 (Box-folder 6/39)
    - Proposed Evaluation Changes, 1989 (Box-folder 6/40)
    - Special Education and Law, 1989 (Box-folder 6/41)
- United Teachers of Everett records, 1975-1992; 3849-006; .03 cubic feet (1 folder)
  Historical feature, memoranda of understanding; 1983-1992. File documents the history of the levy-salary issue. Addition 5/98 of letter dated 12/17/1975 and clipping dated 9/9/1978, also on topic of levy.
  Donated by Mike Sells, 7/18/1997.